{
    "subject": "resource/Troup_County,_Georgia",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Troup County, Georgia",
    "human_readable": "The label of Troup County, Georgia is Troup County, Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9875904321670532,
            "question": "What is the label of Troup County, Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9727903008460999,
            "question": "What information does the label 'Troup County, Georgia' provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9468997716903687,
            "question": "What kind of entity is 'Troup County, Georgia'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7982251644134521,
            "question": "Where is Troup County located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7749125361442566,
            "question": "Is Troup County a geographical location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7455617189407349,
            "question": "What state is Troup County in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7351117730140686,
            "question": "Is there more information about Troup County beyond its label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7311001420021057,
            "question": "How is Troup County identified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6647675037384033,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Troup County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6228798031806946,
            "question": "Does Troup County have a specific name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Troup County, Georgia is Troup County, Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7591_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me something about Troup County?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7591_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Troup County identified?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7591_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there more information about Troup County beyond its label?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7591_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7591_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe triple in question is \"The label of Troup County, Georgia is Troup County, Georgia.\" However, the context information shows that Troup County has multiple labels associated with it, such as being located in west central Georgia, being named after George M. Troup, and having a tag office in LaGrange, GA. Therefore, the statement \"The label of Troup County, Georgia is Troup County, Georgia\" is not accurate, as there are other relevant labels that can be associated with Troup County."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"Troup County, Georgia\" and \"Troup County, Georgia\" are indeed the same labels."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The name of Troup County was not stated as incorrect, but the statement \"the fact 'The label of Troup County, Georgia is Troup County, Georgia.'\" implies that there is an alternative or incorrect label. However, all provided context information consistently states that the name of the county is indeed \"Troup County\", with no indication of any other correct name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}